A Guide to the Alfred Ezra Mirsky papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA131
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Additions to the Alfred Ezra Mirsky Papers
  - Exhibit Catalog, "A View to The East", Selections from The Alfred E. Mirsky Collection, 1985 April (Box 75)
  - Exhibit Catalog, "Katagami: Japanese Textile Stencils," Selections from The Alfred E. Mirsky Collection, 1989 December (Box 75)
  - Exhibit Catalog, "Islamic Pottery," Selections from the Alfred E. Mirsky Collection, 1991 June (Box 75)
  - TS - Untitled
    - re: History of genetics, with annotations, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - re: History of genetics, with annotations, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - re: History of genetics, with annotations, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - re: History of genetics, with annotations, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)